You nauseating Terran filth! Don't think you'll get away with this!
The Cataphract that defeated Sir Vlad, it was orange in color, wasn't it?
I'm not saying anything to a Terran!
Your Sky Carrier transported the Argyre. You saw the whole thing, didn't you?
Yes, I saw everything. I watched that sneaky orange bastard kill him!
Only two orbital knights have been defeated by Terran units, Sir Trollram and Sir Vlad.
And when Sir Trollram suffered his defeat, it was at the hands of an orange Cataphract.
And...Princess of Salem was there with it.
According to this Sky Carrier's data, that Cataphract was aboard a ship traveling a south-by-southwesterly course.
It's not solid proof, maybe a coincidence, but it's the only lead I've got, and I've gotta follow it.
That battle on Tanegashima, my big brother fought in it too. He was killed in action. Murdered, rather, by you.
Mogberej is the name of the family who adopted me. My birth name was Humoray. Your best friend was my only brother, John.
Enemy units are coming in from above! Three more, closing in from our flank! The target is the bridge!
Direct hit! Last target!
Target!
We're done!
I'm out of ammo.
Captain!
And now it ends.
What was that?
I'm not dead?
Hm?
Hmm?
That must be a...
ta-
Okay.
Thank you.
Lord Sazbo, why the delay? Did you not ask that he be captured alive?
If he notices your pursuit, it could affect his destination. I wish to know where it is his plans are leading him.
Meaning what exactly?
What do you think he had in mind when he used the audience chamber?
If he is a spy, then he must have accomplices. Well, no need to worry. I will be tracking every step from overhead.
That was one of their own.
It was, but it kept all of us in one piece.
Martian infighting?
Who knows?
Maybe they're fighting over credit for the kill.
It doesn't really matter. Whether he's our friend or not, our enemy's enemy can be very useful.
What clan does this interloper belong to?
This area belongs to Countess Femi-Anne.
And I will not tolerate you taking liberties here.
Go now. Fly, my messengers.
My messengers.
Botus has been damaged. Now you're done.
Lieutenant Morito. Lieutenant Morito. Are you all right?
Hume-Ray!
Grab on to me, Hume-Ray!
Morito!
Hume-Ray!
I'm getting you out, Hume-Ray!
They're moving too fast!
They've put distance between us. That means...
Attention! Control! Open up the well dock, now!
Ma'am, that's Mustang 2-2!
Captain, young Kaisuka, huh?
All right, do it.
Cover your ears!
Cover your ears, everyone! Please, cover them now!
No!
Hey!
Mommy!
Let's go!
No!
Josh!
I just겠어!
I'm gonna never see it already.
I just want to snuck out of here...
Ah!
Aaaaaah!
We're routes to fly in!
What's that?
A hidden dock?
Engine status.
All are working.
And hull status?
Hull intact.
No, there's a tear.
Make a break for that dock up there, now.
Aye, all ahead, fall.
My love is so picky.
Oh, like a lurking mirror.
This light of heaven that I want you unto.
Beware of the shine.
I'm scared.
I'll make you a heart attack.
Inoho!
Mustang One One!
Come on, Ingo, you're with me.
Huh?
Yes, ma'am.
Right now, burn yourself.
Make your nothing.
Running loud till I know.
Make your rhythm.
Going to push from the rhythm.
To drop your senses back.
Now, where are you going?
You can't just take off.
What about you?
Who's defending the ship?
Listen here, you.
Machine gun fire.
Over the entrance.
Target that rock formation.
But, Captain, fire.
Please be safe.
Hmph.
What does that orange cataphract have up its sleeve now?
Alright.
Now to deal with that steel octopus.
My lord, we are almost close enough for visual search of the Japanese islands.
Once we are within detection range, begin scanning for the sky carrier taken by slain Troyard.
About Princess of Salem.
She is still alive.
I have seen her with my own eyes.
Hmph.
Lord Sosbaum.
We have located the target craft, sir.
Above Tanegashima in the southwestern islands.
The craft appears to be engaging Countess Femian's cataphract, Hellas.
What's that?
Tanegashima, you say?
Wow, what is this place?
I've never heard of a base like this on Tanegashima.
Regardless, get everyone off the ship.
Lieutenant, are you okay?
Lieutenant Morito!
This way!
Let's go!
Try to avoid breathing the smoke!
The civilians have first EBAC priority.
Then the wounded.
No one stays on board.
Yes, sir.
Matsuribi!
Where's Mustang Platoon?
Hinko and the others aren't anywhere on the deck!
They're still fighting on the outside.
We saw them.
They were being decoys for us so we could get away.
That can't be.
Direct hit.
Next target, right three mil.
Roger that.
To get to the assault ship, they'll have to break through all that rock.
To increase their impact, they have to increase their speed.
To accelerate a rocket, you have to have distance.
And if the distance is far enough, throw off the angle a little and it'll miss by a lot.
Huh?
Bogey at four o'clock!
It's turning this way!
Not a problem.
That Martian attack craft will cover us.
How dare you!
What the hell are we doing here?
Yuki, let's hit that enemy cat directly.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
We're no match for that thing.
I'm not so sure.
Could be all bark and no bite there.
Inko, I need to borrow your rifle.
Yeah, alright.
Blocks 11 and 12.
Evac confirmed.
Evacuation of block 8 is also complete.
And so that would be everyone?
That's it.
We should get going now, ma'am.
Has Mustang platoon checked in?
No, ma'am.
Well, then all we can do is pray.
Captain Margberej!
Commander, tell me, where are all our refugees?
I've had them take shelter in a cargo room up ahead so they can rest.
There is something that you need to see, Captain.
You feeling okay?
Is all of this somehow my fault?
Huh?
Just tell me, did it happen because I came to Earth?
Don't think like that.
There would have been no assassination if I had decided not to come.
No assassination.
This war would not be.
Innocent people would not have been made to suffer like this.
You're right.
You should remember that.
Because to these people here, all Martians are the enemy.
How is that even possible?
Cannot begin to say, ma'am.
What kind of installation is this?
Wait! A lady!
Where are you going?
I don't believe it.
A Martian cataphract.
How did it get...
We're in a crater.
It wasn't a single meteor that came down here.
One hit the shore, and the blast formed that bay.
The other one, well, it ended up here.
Wait a minute.
You're saying that this is...
Yeah.
The demon from 15 years ago.
I always figured it was destroyed along with everything else in Heaven's Fall.
Talk about your touching reunion.
Are you saying the UFA did this?
Now hold it!
Then that means for all this time, the report that Lieutenant Marito sent in
was buried just to keep this place a secret?
Even if that's so, is that really all there is to it?
Captain Magberech, look!
Over there!
What in God's name is that?
That orange cat.
Now, what are you doing?
The octopus over there hasn't budged from that one spot.
It keeps repeating the same attack.
I'm pretty sure those are the only weapons it has.
All right.
Give us cover.
Come on, not again!
Inaho!
Are you kidding me?
Contact channel open.
I'll be quick here.
What's your ammo supply?
I have about 20 howitzer rounds.
What about you?
Nine high explosive rounds.
After that, I'm dry.
Wait!
Don't do it now!
That's a Martian!
Sorry, Yuki.
Talk later.
The hell's fists increase their hardness by turning into single molecules.
No bullet can destroy them.
Not accurate.
I destroyed one of them earlier.
Most likely molecular structure reverts when the fingers move.
Patch me into your stabilizer signal.
We use different standards.
No problem.
I can parse it.
Here it comes, Bat.
What's that about?
Little astwo.
All right, especially the ones,.
OOP II.
what are you trying to see?
Don't do it and try it clearly.
We're the duvet.
You're a önce food source, or you'll see them in the dark.
But, at the top, the data journals and migration path
I see you.
We're doing it in the dark later.
Most likely molecular structure reverts?
I don't give outarti.
I'll almost give you away my fingers.
I'm almost the same as the weak bones.
I can easily be able to store you and draftrai.
Just as I thought.
Merex!
I'll get you!
My brother and his crazy stunts.
Come on, we're moving up.
Is that a good idea?
I think so.
Every time he's pulled one, it seems to have been the right choice.
Pull them closer!
One left.
Get directly behind it.
No armor on their tails.
The engines are vulnerable.
Honor 6, two more headed in.
Course 175, fly parallel to the coast.
Yuki, do you copy?
What, you only remember us when you need help?
Maintain that heading!
Bodhis, Merex, Renove, and Halifas, and Rome, and Vine?
How dare you have hurt them?
My children!
We'll fire simultaneously.
Roger.
You leave me no choice!
It just flew away.
Crack!
Hold on, what was that?
I have no idea!
It gained distance again.
Here it comes!
Shoot it to knock it off course!
It's too big for my rifle to move it.
I'm too heavy!
With you aboard, I can't maneuver!
Now I'm going to crush you!
It's gaining on us, Bat!
Just keep quiet, will you, Orange?
This isn't a game!
To lose our altitude, he stalled out?
It's back again.
I've got to level out!
Well, that trick won't work twice!
It's over for you.
What was that?
What the?
What is that?
A flying ship?
It's more.
It's a flying battleship.
Yes, I found you!
Princess of Salem!
Impossible!
The Terrans have no access to all of Noah.
How could they have such a thing?
Enemy craft at 12 o'clock and closing rapidly.
Collision course!
You filthy Terrans!
All right, brace yourself for impact!
Damn you all!
I am still!
For the death of my father.
All Martians will pay the price.
We did it!
That was close!
Princess of Salem!
I found you at last!
Your princess was dead.
But still...
You kept looking for her.
Huh?
You knew that the princess was really alive.
But how?
What do you mean?
Answer me.
Take me to see her highness.
Answer my question first.
Just a minute.
Are you intending to exploit her too?
If she is exploited...
Is that a problem?
What are you saying?
Just tell me!
Are you saying that you're my enemy?
You...
Are my enemy.
It doesn't happen.
Yes!
Would you!
I'm sorry!
You see!
Thank you.